I bet you're oh so happy, Yisho.
You've been pushing for this forever.
Well, you got your wish.
The Seven Warlords have been abolished.
You know I stood firmly against it.
But when the guys at the top make
the call, there's no reversing it.
They should know that justice
comes with a price tag.
Who do you think is paying that price?
Take a step back.
The pity.
Still can't see the
bigger picture, can you?
It's because you've never
been one of the innocent
folks this cruel world has
chewed up and spit out.
Happens every day to good people.
Hurry up!
We don't have time!
Keep moving!
Go, go, go!
The seven warlords are now no more.
Things are gonna get a bit rocky,
so we'll need to put our trust
in our special science group.
The power balance in this world is about
to be turned completely upside down.
That's not the only thing
upside down right now.
Word has it that Kaido and Big
Mom are joining forces in Wano.
That can't be the legendary
Rocks Pirates have returned!
Nothing legendary about this mess.
It's as real as it gets.
And it's our problem to deal with.
Unfortunately, they don't
care how busy we are.
They're just the latest
fiasco on our plate.
Two Emperors of the Sea teamed up?
There's no way.
They're really pulling this right now?
Well, technically speaking, the
intel reports they're about to unite.
There's been no damages as of this moment,
but we don't understand their
motives or how to handle this yet.
We only have a single detail
confirmed at this current time.
They both hail from the
notorious rocks pirates.
Though actual details on the
rocks crew are fairly sparse.
Big Mom and Kaido have been at
odds with one another for ages.
So this is coming out of left field.
Can't say I could have predicted this one.
If I may, who are the Rocks Pirates?
Ah, of course.
You wouldn't know much about them
since they came long before your time.
The Rocks Pirates were a
gang of extremely dangerous
individuals who came together on
the pirate island of Fullalad.
Their entire allegiance was founded
in order to make one big score.
They were such a vicious
bunch of scoundrels
that they'd often kill
their own crewmates.
Captain Rock's lineup consisted
of many heavy hitters.
This included Whitebeard,
Big Mom.
and Kaido.
I know that it's hard to
believe, but trust me,
they were all once part
of the same pirate crew.
What?!
That's crazy!
I can hardly believe that's true!
Amazingly enough,
those three weren't the only crew members
who went on to make a name for themselves.
Just as an example,
some of the other prestigious members
included Chaka the Golden Lion,
The Silver Axe, Captain
John and Wong Ji. Seriously?
All those maniacs were on the same crew
and they didn't wipe each other out?
But how can this story be lost to history?
If they hated their crewmates that much,
well, they wouldn't
want to tell their tale.
Back then, Captain Rocks was
fighting to be king of the world.
They were openly hostile
to the government.
They should have been
considered terrorists.
But many of their incidents
were covered up because
the truth was discomforting
and made us look weak.
Not that it mattered,
but when they ruled the seas, everyone
was well aware of the threat they posed.
Then the news broke out.
The God Valley incident.
Just 38 years ago.
According to the reports,
the fiercest crew in the world,
the Rocks Pirates, had been
completely annihilated on that island.
That rampaging force of evil
that no one was able to stop
before had been crushed by
the Navy Vice Admiral Garp.
His name soon reached
the ends of the world.
That day he became known as
the Great Hero of the Navy.
I knew he was a badass, but I
never heard how he got that title.
He's more than earned it.
I've heard a hundred tales of
heroism about Vice Admiral Garp.
It's hard to believe such an
important one when unnoticed.
He's really taken on all the
big-shot pirates, and he won no less.
Big Mom and Kaido have
allied with each other?
When can we catch a break?
You haven't heard much because the
man himself refuses to talk about it.
Why's that?
Even if he doesn't like it much, I'll tell
you the tale so it isn't lost to history.
There were two reasons why this
was never reported to the presses.
The first being he had to work alongside
pirates in order to win the battle.
Are you joking?
That's not everything.
He protected the Celestial
Dragons in doing so.
Hang on a moment.
How did they tie into all of this?
So what?
Isn't it the Navy's duty
to keep them safe, though?
I don't see a problem.
It's Garp's own moral compass
that tells him otherwise.
A major reason why he's refused the
promotion to Admiral stems from the
fact that it would place him directly
under the Celestial Dragon's command.
It's his accomplishments
and reputation that
prevent him from being
dismissed for insubordination.
Brace yourself for the next part.
Garp had to act quickly to protect the
Celestial Dragons and
their slaves at God Valley.
With no other options left,
he joined forces with Roger.
Together, they pooled their numbers
to defeat the Rock's pirates.
That is the truth of
the God Valley incident.
Like Gold Roger?
King of the Pirates?
They fought together?
Celestial Dragons, Gold
Roger, and the Rocks Pirates?
You listed off so many big names.
Hard to believe all those people
were there at the same time.
How have I not even heard
of this God Valley place?
It's no surprise there.
Look for it on a modern day map.
You won't find that
island's name anywhere.
For good reason, too.
It disappeared without a trace.
The government wanted to hide
what happened on that island,
and they made it disappear.
Knowing this, do you still
want to hear more of the story?
In the end, Rox was thwarted
by his own ambition.
He broke one too many taboos.
The tales of his heinous crimes
were deemed unfit for the public,
and so he came to exist only in legend.
It is a legacy that only lingers in the
memories of a few old
marines from my generation.
It's hard to imagine it.
I know this was years ago,
but it's crazy to think one man
led three of the four emperors.
Captain Rocks was Gold
Roger's very first enemy,
and perhaps his greatest one as well.
That aside, there was something very
interesting that those two had in common.
Though it was rarely spoken, Rock's
full name was Rocks D. Jibak.
He had a special trait some pirates
share, that being the D initial,
although he is no longer
alive to speak of it.
It's true that Kaido and Big Mom were
once shipmates under the same captain.
However, that was 38 years ago, and they
were nothing like they are at the present.
If the intel we received is accurate,
then this would be the birth of the
most dangerous pirate crew in the world.
All right, Brain, why don't you tell
us what everyone's bounties will be?
With pleasure,
but keep in mind that
we'll have to go back to
the drawing board on the
bounties for the Warlords,
since they've had their
immunity stripped away.
As for the other big shots, we
can go over their numbers easily.
Let's start with the
newest Emperor of the Sea,
who attained his title about a year ago.
I'm sure you know.
He gained popularity after
his assault on Impel Down
two years back Now occupying
the pirate island Fuller
-led He continues to expand
his territory and influence
While filling the void
that Whitebeard left behind
Commodore of the Blackbeard
Pirates Marshal D.
Teach 2,247,600,000 berries
As for the next bounty, this man has
been an emperor for six years now.
He's the youngest of the four and
deeply admired by his subordinates,
whom you probably have heard of.
Beckman, Rue, Yasopp.
Each with a high average
bounty themselves.
This pirate crew is world-renowned for
having an excellent balance of skills.
There really are no
weaklings amongst them.
The chief of the Red-Hair Pirates,
Red-Hair Shakes, he's set
at 4,048,900,000 berries!
Now, let's move on.
She was born a monster who
allegedly destroyed an entire
village of giants in Elbath
when she was just a child.
If you're not one of her 85 children,
or at least related by blood, you
will naturally be mistrusted by her.
She's the undisputed queen of the sweet-themed
network of islands known as Totoland.
That is, of course, the captain of the
Big Mom Pirates, Charlotte Lin-Lin.
She's worth 4,388,000,000 berries.
Finally, we have a monster who made
a name for himself early on in life.
This man was only an apprentice
when he joined the Rock's crew.
He won the respect of the most ferocious
of pirates through his
sheer strength alone,
until he was worthy of earning
the title Emperor of the Sea.
Supreme Commander of
the Beast Pirates Kaido,
King of the Beasts Worth
4,611,100,000 Berries
How distressing Now it goes without
saying But they decided at the
reverie That we will no longer
have the Warlords at our disposal
only time will tell if distancing ourselves
was a good decision or not we'll have
to wait and see how the navy's special
science team the ssg
performs since we're here
i'll put this in perspective i might as
well share the bounties
of some other legends
the captain of the white beard pirates
edward newgate 5 billion
46 million berries
The captain of the Roger
Pirates The king of the
pirates Gold Roger 5 billion
564 million 800 thousand
There hasn't been a bounty to
surpass these two At least not yet
But if Big Mom and Kaido
form their alliance,
their combined bounty will be the
highest the world has ever seen,
and the size of their crew will be huge.
I've read the reports.
This is happening as we speak in Wano.
Fleet Admiral Sakazuki.
We won't be getting involved with that.
In case you went senile,
we lack the manpower and resources
to handle this currently.
Any questions?
None.
I never intended to get involved anyway.
This old man was simply
providing these young
soldiers with some wisdom and experience.
At the end of the day, pirates are humans.
They have their own
relationships and reasons.
You can't take action without
knowing their history.
Speaking of which, there was a pirate
from Wano who Whitebeard was fond of.
He was favored by Roger and Red Hair.
You mean Kozuki Odin, don't you?
The man who served as a commander
on Whitebeard's ship long ago.
None other, of course.
And that's not all he did.
The King of the Pirates recruited
him for his final journey.
Something's not adding up.
While I can't imagine Odin
being connected, it seems odd.
Doesn't it make you question
why all these huge players have
such close ties to an isolated
country like the land of Wano?
I can't believe it's coincidence.
You do well to keep your
eyes open, Sakazuki.